During the Sunday Service at The SCOAN Prophet T.B. Joshua is used as an instrument of the power of God,
severing the chains of affliction in people's lives.
Among those who received that freedom is this young lady.
As she encounters the light of God, every darkness within her is exposed,
and the spirit tormenting her begins to confess.
Who are you?!
Hatred.
How many of you are in this body?
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am affliction.
Speak out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I entered her at the cemetery.
What have you done to her marriage?
I killed.
Deliverance In Jesus’ Name
TESTIMONY TIME
Good Morning!
Emmanuel!
Murtazina Anastasia
Kazakstan
Glory be to God!
I thank God for all His love and for my deliverance.
He brought me here and fulfilled His promise which He gave me before.
I am very thankful to Him.
God put in my heart that, once I was delivered, my whole family would be delivered.
So, we thank God.
We can see you are overcome by what God has done not only in your life but in your entire family.
Right now we want to hear from you; exactly how this spirit entered your life,
and what were you delivered from.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
The Lord delivered me from the spirit of hatred, generational curses, afflictions and the spirit of lust.
From childhood, I was told that my grandmother from my father’s side was mentally ill,
that she walked on the edge of the rooftop and that I resembled her.
They said it because I was a disobedient child.
Very often, I witnessed how my mother and grandmother fought and cursed each other.
I hated it.
I tried to stop them.
My sister and I were also doing the same thing because we were living the same environment.
We would curse our grandmother, mother and each other because we thought it was a joke.
When I was six or seven years old, my mother was possessed by the spirit of lust.
I have two sisters; we are three girls and all of us are from different fathers.
My mother would often leave us with our grandmother and go out with different men.
She was busy building her own life.
My grandmother was addicted to alcohol and would beat us.
I felt her hatred towards us and wariness was due to her having to take care of us.
Where was a spirit of lust inside of me.
I remember that my mother loved us very much.
She would take us for weekends.
I remember the day I heart her screaming in the night.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I woke up and saw my mother sleeping with a man.
Then, the spirit of lust entered into me. I was eight years old.
Later on, my mother died due to blood cancer at the age of 31.
I was 11 or 12 years old.
My grandmother was yearning for her and a month later, she also died.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
My relatives took us into their care.
They often blamed me, telling me I was the cause of the death of my mother and grandmother.
I hated myself and wanted to commit suicide.
I would take tablets.
Nobody knew but God kept rescuing me.
When I was 12 years old, I was given a book to read about ancient Greek mythologies.
I found out that there were different gods and often identified myself with the goddess Athena -
the goddess of war and discord.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
There was a lot of hatred inside of me because I was beaten and blamed for their deaths.
Due to the absence of love, I didn’t feel loved and so would masturbate a lot.
I would often cry, blaming my mother for leaving me.
There were moments when, as a student studying for my diploma,
I would spend a lot of time on the internet.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I found a book in which was a dedication to the spirits of the elements – water, fire and air.
I dedicated myself and my entire generation.
Then, I couldn’t sleep for 10 days but after that,
I dreamt that a man in a white garment married me; he would come to me and sleep with me.
Later, at The SCOAN, it was revealed to me that this man was a spirit of fire and dragon.
I started to speak in different demonic tongues and something tried to strangle me.
At the same time, I stared to spend a lot of time in the cemetery crying, longing for my mum.
In the cemetery, I was experiencing aggression and anger.
I was certain that I had left my hair behind on the gravestones of other people.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
Later, I broke up with my boyfriend because I wasn’t happy with him.
I started to visit gay clubs.
Initially, I thought that it was not normal to have many men but something happened
which increased my urge to meet with more men.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I started to have different desires and would watch sexual movies on the internet.
A feeling of guilt smothered me and I later found a magazine in which was written,
“I will help you in everything”.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I went to visit the place that used that slogan; their teaching was based on cosmo energy.
I was dedicated to spiritual channels; I desired and chose them.
They were similar to the myths of ancient Greece.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
They told me that those practices were good.
They encouraged me to have relationships with many men.
They told me that it would develop me physically.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
After you were initiated into this cult of cosmo-energy through the internet,
can you tell us now, what happened to those men that you slept with?
What happened to their lives?
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I applied these spiritual channels to men.
Before I got acquainted with cosmo energetic teaching, I didn’t use them.
The men would all be very unhappy.
I made them miserable; I would beat them.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
It was a special day when, by chance, I found internet videos about deliverance from evil spirits.
Initially, something turned inside of me and I didn’t want to see it.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I knew that something was wrong.
It was not just a simple desire – it was something strange, alien.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I knew because I was communicating with those spirits.
I had two dreams about Prophet T.B. Joshua before my trip to The SCOAN.
He told me that I was free.
Before coming here, I received a word that once I was delivered,
my family would be delivered too.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
What was your experience during that deliverance, and how was your life changed?
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
I had a huge spirit of fear.
The spirit in me wanted to hide itself behind people.
I had a sense that something would come upon me and force me to leave.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
When Prophet T.B. Joshua came to me, my teeth started to chatter.
I clung to a woman and something was crying inside of me; it was not my usual cry.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
The evil spirits that were inside of me started to leave, including the spirit of mermaid.
I also had a vision that a crayfish came out from my leg.
At that time, there was a lump on my leg that I wanted to be free from.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
She said immediately Prophet T.B. Joshua touched her, the power of the Holy Spirit came on her,
she saw the spirit of the mermaid leave her, she saw crabs crawling out of her body.
She said there was a tumour on her ankle before and it disappeared after her deliverance.
This is the physical manifestation of the deliverance in her life.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Besides that, I suffered from an allergy for 14 years but when I came here to the arena of liberty,
I was able to smell the flowers and enjoy their scent.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
Can you tell us now, how are you now after your deliverance?
I am happy; I can read my Bible.
I feel a sense of unity with God, the Father.
I know that He will always care about me, that I am a daughter of the King.
I know that through this testimony, I have my crown from He who delivered me.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
Thank You, Jesus!
There is nothing impossible for our God, Jesus Christ.
All glory be to the Lord that He delivered me and my entire family.
Hallelujah!
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
Have faith in God; trust in God always, until the end.
Follow Him.
I am a living testimony that God is and that He is alive.
Murtazina Anastasia
Deliverance Testimony
We thank God for your deliverance and we want to encourage you to stay close to Jesus Christ,
to maintain your wonderful freedom, in Jesus' name.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 09/11/2018